let questions = [
    {
        numb:1 ,
        question: " Which is the capital of Morocco?",
        answer: "Rabat",
        options: [
          "Tripoli",
          "Rabat",
          "Khartoum",
          "Addis Ababa"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb:2,
        question: " Which territory under Morocco is disputed?",
        answer: " Western Sahara",
        options: [
          "Abkhazia",
          "Somaliland",
          "South Ossetia",
          "Western Sahara"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which famous film has the name of a city of Morocco? ",
        answer: "Casablanca",
        options: [
          "Marrakesh",
          "Casablanca",
          "Fes",
          "Tangier"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb:4 ,
        question: "When did France and Spain divide Morocco into their zones of influence? ",
        answer: "1904",
        options: [
          "1912",
          "1956",
          "1904",
          "1900"
        ]
      },

      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which country is to the east of Morocco? ",
        answer: "Algeria",
        options: [
          "Algeria",
          "Angola",
          "Ghana",
          "Ivory Coast"
        ]
      },

      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which is the currency of Morocco? ",
        answer: "Dirham",
        options: [ 
        
          "Dinar",
          "Riyal",
          "Dirham",
          "Rupee"
        ]
      },

      {
        numb:7 ,
        question: "Which is the official language of Morocco? ",
        answer: "Arabic",
        options: [
            
          "Arabic",
          "Persian",
          "Turkish",
          "Dari"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb:8 ,
        question: "Who became the King of Morocco in 1999? ",
        answer: "Mohammed VI",
        options: [
            
          "Mohammed VI",
          "Mohammed III",
          "Hassan I",
          "Hassan II"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb:9 ,
        question: " What is in the centre of Moroccoâ€™s national flag?",
        answer: "Five pointed green star",
        options: [ 
            
          "Red star",
          "Sun",
          "Wheel",
          "Five pointed green star"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb:10 ,
        question: " What is the date of Marrakesh Declaration? ",
        answer: "15 April 1994",
        options: [
            
          "20 September 1986",
          "15 April 1994",
          "1 January 1999",
          "1 January 2002"
        ]
      },


    ];